wearvr.com 2018-10-16

# Privacy policy - WEARVR

WEARVR, LLC (“we”, “our”, “us” or “WEARVR”) respects the privacy of its online visitors and users of its products and services. We have adopted this privacy policy to be transparent about how WEARVR collects, stores, and uses information derived from users’ interaction with WEARVR products, services and online sites.

This policy is current as of its last revision date. However, please note that this policy document may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to WEARVR’s privacy policy. Any changes to our policy will be posted to the website and we will notify you of these changes, for example, by email, when it is appropriate and technically feasible to do so.

This privacy policy was last updated: 24/05/2018

## Contact Details

If you have any queries or requests concerning this privacy policy or how we handle your data more generally, please contact our Data Protection Officer on [dpo@wearvr.com](mailto:dpo@wearvr.com).

If you are concerned about the accuracy of personally identifiable information maintained by WEARVR or wish to review, access, amend or correct it, or would like your personally identifiable information removed from WEARVR’s records or otherwise deactivated, please contact us at [privacy@wearvr.com](mailto:privacy@wearvr.com).

## What Information We Collect

Technical data such as IP addresses, device id, user agents and operating system version may be logged for analytics, monitoring, security and stability purposes when using any of WEARVR’s products or services.

When you sign up for any of our email newsletters, promotions or referral programs, we store your email address while you remain a subscriber. You can unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe link included in every email.

When you create a user account, we will ask you for enough information to create you an account that only you can log in to. If you upgrade to a developer account, we may collect additional contact details and ask you to review the information you have already associated with your account.

We keep a record of some of the actions you may perform as you interact with our products and services, such as downloading, rating or commenting. When you make a purchase our payment processors will store the financial details necessary to complete the transaction. We also request and store billing address information for European Union (EU) customers.

We may store any information you include in messages you post on, or through, any of WEARVR’s products or services or third party services or accounts belonging to WEARVR. This includes sending messages via contact, comment or feedback forms, or to our email accounts.

If you have a developer account, we store information related to the virtual reality content you have listed on WEARVR, as well as statistical information of how users have interacted with that content. We may request and store further personal information necessary for you to do business with us or our partners; if this happens, we will explain in advance what information we need, why we need it and who will have access to it.

External websites and companies with links to and from WEARVR’s online sites and products may collect personally identifiable information about users. Third party publishers may also collect personally identifiable information as a requirement of accessing their virtual reality games or body. WEARVR’s privacy policy does not extend to these external websites and companies or third party publishers. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies.

## Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We only process your information when we have a lawful basis for doing so and there is a reason permitted under data protection law. This basis may be: we need to process your information to provide you with one or more of the WEARVR products or services you have requested, or to enter into a contract; you have given us your consent; we have a justifiable reason for processing your data; or we are legally required to do so.

We process the technical and analytic data we collect to develop, deliver and improve our products, body and services. We use this data to maintain the quality and availability of the services we offer.

Purchase, download and other account activity information is used to improve the accuracy of our statistical information (such as download and view figures) and to protect and secure the content that appears on our products and services. We do not share individual user account activity with anyone other than the user that the data relates to.

We store comments and ratings you submit and we may display them next to the content that it relates to, where it is visible to other users of our products or services. We will not share or make public any messages sent via email or a similarly private or direct means of communication, unless you advise us that you would like us to do so.

We use email addresses provided by users who signed up to our email newsletter to send information about WEARVR, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials, but only if the users agree to receive such communications.

We may use the information we have collected from developers to pay them for the content they have sold through WEARVR’s products and services, or its partners. We may also contact developers via email, from time to time, to discuss or notify them of matters relating to their existing or future virtual reality content, or to discuss opportunities or developments we believe they may be interested in.

## Who Has Access To Your Information

WEARVR will not share personally identifiable information with other parties except as described in this policy.

WEARVR may allow third parties performing services under contract with WEARVR to access and use personally identifiable information, but only to the extent necessary to provide those services.

The types of third party service providers whom we may share your information with include:

  *  **Payment providers:** for the purposes of providing services to us, for example when they process information such as credit card payments for us, provide support services to you or carry out fraud checks for us;
  *  **IT service providers:** for the purposes of data storage, service delivery and analysis;
  *  **Deployment services:** for the purposes of error logging and service monitoring;
  *  **Mailing list managers:** for the purposes of managing email subscriptions and sending information.
  *  **Device or platform partners:** for the purposes of distributing developer’s virtual reality content to new platforms or markets. We will never do this without first receiving your written permission.

These service providers may have servers that store information outside of the EU.

WEARVR may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information.

In the event of a reorganization, sale or merger, we may transfer personally identifiable information to the relevant third party.

## Cookies

When you browse any of our sites, we may store cookies in your browser to help keep you logged in, save your place, record your settings or preferences, remember your previous actions, personalise your experience or give access to new or exclusive features or services.

WEARVR may also use analytic tools that use cookies to collect information concerning general usage of our websites, such as referring web addresses, page views and browser types.

You can set your browser to disable or delete some or all of these cookies. If you chose to do so, some areas and functionality of the site may cease to function correctly or become inaccessible.

## Retention of Personally Identifiable Information

We will not store any of your data for any longer than we think is necessary. Information that we collect will be retained for as long as needed to fulfil the purposes outlined above in “Use of Personally Identifiable Information”, in line with our legitimate interest or for a period specifically required by applicable regulations or laws, such as retaining the information for regulatory reporting purposes.

When determining the relevant retention periods, we will take into account factors including:

  * Our contractual obligations and rights in relation to the information involved;
  * Legal obligations under applicable law to retain data for a certain period of time;
  * Statute of limitations under applicable law;
  * Our legitimate interests where we have carried out balancing tests;
  * Potential disputes;
  * Guidelines issued by relevant data protection authorities;

Otherwise, we securely erase your information where we no longer require it for the purposes collected.

## Your Rights

Under data protection law, you may have a number of rights concerning the data we hold about you.

  *  **The right to be informed:** You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your information and your rights. This is why we’re providing you with the information in this policy.
  *  **The right of access:** You have the right to obtain access to your information. This will enable you, for example, to check that we’re using your information in accordance with data protection law. If you wish to access the information we hold about you in this way, please get in touch (see Contact Details).
  *  **The right to rectification:** You are entitled to have your information corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete. You can request that we rectify any errors in information that we hold by contacting us (see Contact Details).
  *  **The right to erasure:** This is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’ and, in simple terms, enables you to request the deletion or removal of certain information that we hold about you by contacting us (see Contact Details).
  *  **The right to restrict processing:** You have rights to ‘block’ or ‘suppress’ further use of your information. When processing is restricted, we can still store your information, but will not use it further.
  *  **The right to data portability:** You have the right to obtain your personal information in an accessible and transferable format so that you can re-use it for your own purposes across different service providers. This is not a general right however and there are exceptions. To learn more please get in touch (see Contact Details).
  *  **The right to lodge a complaint:** You have the right to lodge a complaint about the way we handle or process your information with the national data protection authority (See Complaints).
  *  **The right to withdraw consent:** If you have given your consent to anything we do with your information (i.e. we rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your information), you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. You can do this by contacting us (see Contact Details).
  *  **The right to object to processing:** You have the right to object to certain types of processing, including processing for direct marketing and profiling. You can object by clicking the “unsubscribe” link, which is at the bottom of all direct marketing correspondence.

## Complaints

If you’re not satisfied with our response to any complaint or you believe our processing of your information does not comply with data protection law, you can make a complaint to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) using the following details:

Address: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire SK9 5AF

Telephone number: 0303 123 1113

www.ico.org.uk
